ozgrid.com 2019-12-25

# Terms and Conditions / Privacy Policy

Terms and Conditions

  1. [Home](https://www.ozgrid.com/index.php)
  2. Terms and Conditions

Welcome to **www.ozgrid.com.** If you continue to browse and use this website, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern OzGrid Business Applications relationship with you in relation to this website. If you disagree with any part of these terms and conditions, please do not use our website.

The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use:

The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.  
This website uses cookies to monitor browsing preferences. If you do allow cookies to be used, some personal information may be stored by us.  We do not provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law. Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.  
This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.  
All trade marks reproduced in this website which are not the property of, or licensed to, the operator are acknowledged on the website.  
Unauthorised use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offence.  From time to time this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).  
Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to Australian law.

* * *

**OzGrid Business Applications** is committed to providing quality services to you and this policy outlines our ongoing obligations to you in respect of how we manage your Personal Information.

We have adopted the Australian Privacy Principles (APPs) contained in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (the Privacy Act). The NPPs govern the way in which we collect, use, disclose, store, secure and dispose of your Personal Information.

A copy of the Australian Privacy Principles may be obtained from the website of The Office of the Australian Information Commissioner at [www.aoic.gov.au](http://www.aoic.gov.au/)

**What is Personal Information and why do we collect it?**

Personal Information is information or an opinion that identifies an individual. Examples of Personal Information we collect include: names, addresses, email addresses, phone and facsimile numbers.

This Personal Information is obtained in many ways including correspondence, email, via our website [www.ozgrid.com](http://www.ozgrid/), from your website, from media and publications, from other publicly available sources, from cookies, and from third parties. We don’t guarantee website links or policy of authorised third parties.

We collect your Personal Information for the primary purpose of providing our services to you, providing information to our clients and marketing. We may also use your Personal Information for secondary purposes closely related to the primary purpose, in circumstances where you would reasonably expect such use or disclosure.  **PLEASE NOTE -**   We will never give or sell your personal information to anyone unless you authorise it.  It is only for our own use.

When we collect Personal Information we will, where appropriate and where possible, explain to you why we are collecting the information and how we plan to use it.

**Sensitive Information**

Sensitive information is defined in the Privacy Act to include information or opinion about such things as an individual's racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, membership of a political association, religious or philosophical beliefs, membership of a trade union or other professional body, criminal record or health information.

Sensitive information will be used by us only:

  * For the primary purpose for which it was obtained
  * For a secondary purpose that is directly related to the primary purpose
  * With your consent; or where required or authorised by law.

**Third Parties**

Where reasonable and practicable to do so, we will collect your Personal Information only from you. However, in some circumstances we may be provided with information by third parties. In such a case we will take reasonable steps to ensure that you are made aware of the information provided to us by the third party.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

Your Personal Information may be disclosed in a number of circumstances including the following:

  * Third parties where you consent to the use or disclosure; and
  * Where required or authorised by law.

**Security of Personal Information**

Your Personal Information is stored in a manner that reasonably protects it from misuse and loss and from unauthorized access, modification or disclosure.

When your Personal Information is no longer needed for the purpose for which it was obtained, we will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify your Personal Information. However, most of the Personal Information is or will be stored in client files which will be kept by us for a minimum of 7 years.

**Access to your Personal Information**

You may access the Personal Information we hold about you and to update and/or correct it, subject to certain exceptions. If you wish to access your Personal Information, please contact us in writing.

OzGrid Business Applications will not charge any fee for your access request, but may charge an administrative fee for providing a copy of your Personal Information.

In order to protect your Personal Information we may require identification from you before releasing the requested information.

**Maintaining the Quality of your Personal Information**

It is an important to us that your Personal Information is up to date. We  will  take reasonable steps to make sure that your Personal Information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. If you find that the information we have is not up to date or is inaccurate, please advise us as soon as practicable so we can update our records and ensure we can continue to provide quality services to you.

**Policy Updates**

This Policy may change from time to time and is available on our website.

**Privacy Policy Complaints and Enquiries**

If you have any queries or complaints about our Privacy Policy please contact us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

* * *

**OzGrid Business Applications** may use cookies, web beacons, tracking pixels, and other tracking technologies when you visit our website www.ozgrid.com, including any other media form, media channel, mobile website, or mobile application related or connected thereto (collectively, the “Site”) to help customize the Site and improve your experience.

We reserve the right to make changes to this Cookie Policy at any time and for any reason. We will alert you about any changes by updating the “Last Updated” date of this Cookie Policy. Any changes or modifications will be effective immediately upon posting the updated Cookie Policy on the Site, and you waive the right to receive specific notice of each such change or modification.

You are encouraged to periodically review this Cookie Policy to stay informed of updates. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted the changes in any revised Cookie Policy by your continued use of the Site after the date such revised Cookie Policy is posted.

**USE OF COOKIES**

A “cookie” is a string of information which assigns you a unique identifier that we store on your computer. Your browser then provides that unique identifier to use each time you submit a query to the Site. We use cookies on the Site to, among other things, keep track of services you have used, record registration information, record your user preferences, keep you logged into the Site, facilitate purchase procedures, and track the pages you visit. Cookies help us understand how the Site is being used and improve your user experience.

**TYPES OF COOKIES**

The following types of cookies may be used when you visit the Site:

**Advertising Cookies**

Advertising cookies are placed on your computer by advertisers and ad servers in order to display advertisements that are most likely to be of interest to you. These cookies allow advertisers and ad servers to gather information about your visits to the Site and other websites, alternate the ads sent to a specific computer, and track how often an ad has been viewed and by whom. These cookies are linked to a computer and do not gather any personal information about you.

**Analytics Cookies**

Analytics cookies monitor how users reached the Site, and how they interact with and move around once on the Site. These cookies let us know what features on the Site are working the best and what features on the Site can be improved.

**Our Cookies**

Our cookies are “first-party cookies”, and can be either permanent or temporary. These are necessary cookies, without which the Site won't work properly or be able to provide certain features and functionalities. Some of these may be manually disabled in your browser, but may affect the functionality of the Site.

**Personalization Cookies**

Personalization cookies are used to recognize repeat visitors to the Site. We use these cookies to record your browsing history, the pages you have visited, and your settings and preferences each time you visit the Site.

**Security Cookies**

Security cookies help identify and prevent security risks. We use these cookies to authenticate users and protect user data from unauthorized parties.

**Site Management Cookies**

Site management cookies are used to maintain your identity or session on the Site so that you are not logged off unexpectedly, and any information you enter is retained from page to page. These cookies cannot be turned off individually, but you can disable all cookies in your browser.

**Third-Party Cookies**

Third-party cookies may be place on your computer when you visit the Site by companies that run certain services we offer. These cookies allow the third parties to gather and track certain information about you. These cookies can be manually disabled in your browser.

**Control of Cookies**

Most browsers are set to accept cookies by default. However, you can remove or reject cookies in your browser’s settings. Please be aware that such action could affect the availability and functionality of the Site.

For more information on how to control cookies, check your browser or device’s settings for how you can control or reject cookies.

* * *

We continually strive to become ' **the** ' site for anything Spreadsheet related so we aim for complete customer satisfaction by offering a  _ ** _30 DAY MONEY BACK GUARANTEE_**_  on most products. 

 _ **We add no margin to 3rd party products**_

 and make our money through commission only. This allows us to  **give-away our products  **on some purchases and  **help in after sales service**
